{
    "questions": [
 
        {   
           
            "questionText": "t p a s",
            "answers": "past"
        },
        {
            
            "questionText": "c d l o",
            "answers":"cold"
        },
        {
            
            "questionText": "n s d e",
            "answers":"send" 
        },
        {
            
            "questionText": "y t i d",
            "answers":"tidy" 
        },
        {
            
            "questionText": "n k i t",
            "answers":"knit" 
        },
        {
            
            "questionText": "d e i h",
            "answers":"hide" 
        },
        {
            
            "questionText": "a r f e",
            "answers":"fear" 
        },
        {
            
            "questionText": "u h p s",
            "answers":"push" 
        },
        {
            
            "questionText": "s e i w",
            "answers":"wise" 
        },
        {
            
            "questionText": "a d g r",
            "answers":"drag" 
        }
 
    ],
    "type":"Hard"
}
